UNITE Legislative Department Records 6000/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Fair Minimum Wage Act of 1999 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Minimum Wage 2000 106th Congress (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Minimum Wage 2000: S. 2284 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Minimum Wage Task Force Meeting Notes 1999 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Minimum Wage: 1997 Increase (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Minimum Wage Background, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Misc. Bills, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Motor Voter: Horn Bill H.R. 1428, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Motor Voter: Impact Reports, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Multiple Jobholding, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- NAPP Technologies, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- National Alliance of Postal and Federal Employees (Box 11, Folder 8)
- NBCSL, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- NCSL, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- National Guard Uniforms, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- NLRB, 1993-1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- National Retail Federation, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- New York Apparel Industry, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- New York Laundry Master Agreement, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Nonstandard Work Arrangements, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Northern Marianas 106th Congress, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- No. Marianas/AFL Project, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Northern Marianas: Dept. of Justice, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Northern Marianas: Lawsuit-Unite Stuff Folder #1, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Northern Marianas: Lawsuit-Unite Stuff Folder #2, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- No. Marianas/Miller Report, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- No. Marianas/Labor Contract (Box 11, Folder 23)
- No. Marianas/Supportive Organization, 1997-2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- No. Marianas/Miller Bill - HR730, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- No. Marianas/Lawsuit Unite Stuff, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- No. Marianas/Taxes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- No. Marianas/Freedom House, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- No. Marianas/106 Cong. Legis, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- No. Marianas/1999 Lawsuit Press (Box 11, Folder 30)
- No. Marianas/Unite Suit, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Nurses, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Nursing Homes: DOL Initiative, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- OECD, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs (OFCCP), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Organizing, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- OSHA Bill - ENZI Bill, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- PAC Contribution Request, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Part Time Worker Bill, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Patients Bill of Rights 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Pay Equity - 106th Congress, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Pay Equity: NCPE Information, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Paycheck Fairness Act 105th Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Pay Equity: Maryland Network, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Pay Equity: State Activity, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Pay Equity: Wage Gap Briefing 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Pendleton Woolen Mills, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Hats, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Pensions 2001, 1996-2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Pension, 1996-2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Pensions: Kennedy Plan 2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia Inquirer Series, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Photographs, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Pharmaceutical Industry Labor Management Committee, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Pogo, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Polling, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Political Department, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Post Office Uniforms, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- New Postal Uniform Letters, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Postal Uniforms: Concurrent Res., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Poultry Project: Department of Labor, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Prescription Drugs, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Pre-Paid Legal Services HR-1434 2002, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Privatization, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Procurement - Unite Program, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Procurement NYC Ordinance, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Procurement Briefing, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Project Labor Agreements, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Proposition 226, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Proposed Generic Drug Bill, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Quaker Fabric, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Retail, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Right Start Act of 2001 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- 104th Congress - Right to Work, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Right to Work '96, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Right to Work, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Royal Airlines Laundry, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- San Francisco Garment 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Sara Lee, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Schawb Corporation Strike, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Secretary of Labor, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- "Secret Evidence", 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Senate Rules, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Sexual Harassment, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Social Security 107th Congress, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Social Security 2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Social Security: Bush's Plan, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Social Security Commission, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Social Security: NCPSSM/Privatizing, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Social Security Name Checks, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Privatizing Social Security, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Social Security Santorum Letters, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Social Security: Stock Market Investment, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Sorrento Coats, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- State Legislation, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Steelworkers Grassroots Progress, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Temp Agencies, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Textile Industry, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Toledo's Van Dyne Crotty, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Tort Reform, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Trafficking in People, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Truck Drivers, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Responding to the President's Social Security Commission and Release of Final Commission Report, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Unemployment, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Unemployment Insurance, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Devolve Unemployment, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- TSA Screeners - Uniforms, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Union Advantage, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Union Label, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Unite Basic Education Programs, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Unite Hispanic Members Political Mobilization, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Unite Members Correspondence to Congressional Members (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Unite Organizing, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Unite Procurement Campaign 1999 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Unite Targeting Plan 2000 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Unite Translations, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- United for a Fair Economy, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- United Nations Code of Conduct, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- United Students Against Sweatshops, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Van Dyne Crotty, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Vieques - PR, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Voting Records Individuals, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Unite Voter Guide 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Votes Senate 106th, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- House 106th, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- 107th Congressional Voting Record, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Voting Record 1947-1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Voting Record 1980-1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Congressman Rick Boucher - Voting Record, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Senator Lieberman - Voting Record, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Wages, Benefits Etc., in Apparel & Footwear, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Wages & Globalization, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Warn Act, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Washington Office on Africa (WOA), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Washington Union Women, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Washington University in St. Louis, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Wellman Polyester Problem, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Welfare Reform: Results, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Women & Work, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Women and Retirement Security, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Women's Wear Companies, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Women Workers - Occupational Segregation, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Worker Classification Bill 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Workers in the Global Economy (WGE), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Census 2000, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Women and the Global Economy, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Women in Unions, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Women on a Roll, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- WTO & Labor Rights, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Work: Family Issues, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Elder Care, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Workforce Investment Act, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Trade: 107th Congress, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Trade: ACTPN, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Trade: ACPTN Flap, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Trade: Admin. Position & AFL-CIO Oct. 99, 1999-2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Trade: AFL-CIO Globalization Campaign, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Trade: AFL-CIO Positions, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Trade: AFL-CIO Sierra Club Program, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- African Trade Act 2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Trade: Africa - AIDS, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Trade: African American Impact, 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Trade: Africa - Bad Press, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Trade: Africa - April 21 Demo, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Trade: Africa Background 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- HR 434 Vote African Growth, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Africa Trade (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Trade - Africa - Free Trade Agreement, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Trade: Africa Growth - Carol September, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Trade: Africa - Hope Cosponsors, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Trade: African Growth S.1387 106th Congress, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Statement of Mark Levinson 2/3/99, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Trade: Africa - NAACP, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Trade: Africa Regs, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Africa Testimony, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Trade: Africa Free Trade Agmt. Clean Clothes Report, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Trade: Africa Free Trade Agmt. 106th Congress - Dear Colleagues, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Trade: Africa Free Trade Agr. Facts, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Trade: Africa Free Trade Agmt. H.R. 1432 Votes, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Trade - Africa Free Trade HR1432, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Trade: Africa Free Trade Admend. Senate Status, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Africa Free Trade Agreement Unite Lobby Day 7/16/98, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Trade: Africa Free Trade Agmt. South Africa Views, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Trade: Africa Hope for Africa Act, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Africa: Rangel Comments, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Africa Free Trade Agreement UNITE's Testimony, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Trade: African Growth - Senate HR434, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Trade: Africa - Ways & Means Cmte. H.R. 434, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Trade: Agriculture, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Trade: AIDS, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Trade: Alternative for the Americas, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Trade: Alternative Model, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Trade: Amerisource Alliance, Inc., 2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Trade: Andean trade Preference Act 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Trade: Antidumping, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- ATMI Flip, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Trade: Basics, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Trade: Brofenbrenner Report, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Trade: Business Wins, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Trade: Catholics, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- CBI/Africa: Implementation AFL Comments, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- CBI Implementation: Africa 2000 Aftermath (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Trade: CBI/Africa Implementation - Dyeing, Etc., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- CBI/Africa - Implementation Sweater Issue, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- CBI/Implementation: Socks, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- CBI Implementation: Worker Rights, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Trade: CBI/Africa - 2000 Implementation (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Trade: CBI Parity ITC Report 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Trade: CBI/Africa - 2000 HR434 Managers Report (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Trade: CBI/Africa - HR434 Final, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Trade: CBI/Africa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Trade: CBI 99 Bodner/Mazur Release, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- EPI Reports - CBI, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Trade: CBI 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Trade: CBI 99 - 106th Congress Meeting Notes, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Trade: CBI Parity - HR984 106th Congress, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Trade: CBI Regs, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- CBI: HR2644, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Trade: CBI Parity Year End Effort 1998 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Trade: CBI NY Letter, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Various Documents 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Trade: CBI Vote, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Trade: CBI - Worker Rights, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Central America 2002 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Trade: Chile, 1997-2001 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Trade: China WTO - 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Trade: China WTO - Aftermath, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Trade: China WTO Legal, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Trade: China WTO - 106th Congress, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- trade: China - WTO - Unite Stuff, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Trade: China Visits, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- China WTO 2000 Ways & Means Hearing 2/16/2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Trade: Colombia, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Trade: Columbia - Material for Visits, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Trade: Competition Between Countries, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Trade: 107th Congress Positions, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Trade: CTC - Trade Principles (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Trade: CTC 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Country of Origin Labeling, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Trade: Customs Enforcement & Market Access Act, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Trade: Deficit Review Commission, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Trade: Deficit Review Commission Report, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Trade: Enforcement, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Trade: Enviro, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Trade: EPI Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Trade: Economic Policy Institute, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Trade: EPI Group (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Fast Track HR3005 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Trade: Fast Track 106th Congress Public Citizen Proposal, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Fast Track - 107th Congress CTC Briefing, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Trade: Fast Track - 107th Congress, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Fast Track: ILO Issue 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Fast Track: Agriculture, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Fast Track: UNITE Political Dept. Mailings, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Trade: Fast Track - Deals, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Fast track: Not Necessary, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Trade: Fast Track DLC Piece, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Fast Track: Layoffs by A lot, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Fast Track: Enviros, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Fast Track: Florida, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Trade: Fast Track Food Safety, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Trade: Fast Track Gephardt Draft, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Fast Track Gephardt Proposal, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Fast Track: Gephardt Meetings, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Trade: Fast Track Human Rights Letter, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- trade: Fast Track - LCCR, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Trade: Fast Track Mazur "No Money", 1997 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Trade: Fast Track - IUD, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Trade: Fast Track Organization Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Trade: Fast track - Groups Religious, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Trade: Harmonization, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Trade: Fast Track Jay's Activities, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Fast Track: Job Loss, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Fast Track Conference 2001 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Trade: Fast Track State Activity, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Trade: Fast Track "Vote" Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Fast Track: Textile Deal 2002 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Trade: Fast Track - TAA, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Fast Track: Ways & Means Hearing, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Fast Track: Ways & Means 10/8/97, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Trade: Food Safety, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Trade: Food Labeling, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Trade: FTAA Southern Opposition, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Trade: Free Trade Agreement of Americas, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Trade: Free Trade Agmt. Of the Americas - Committee on Civil Society, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Trade: FTAA, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Trade: GSP, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Trade: Garment Workers Impact, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Trade: Globalization Follies, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Trade: Global Textile Competitiveness, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Trade: Guatemala GSP, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Trade: Guest Workers, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Trade: Gundersheim Memos, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Trade: Gundersheim Testimony, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Trade: Haiti, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Trade: India, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Trade: Inter-County Job Shifts, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Trade: Int'l Trade Commission (ITC), 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Trade: Labor Austr, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- July 15, 1998 Lobby Day Trade (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Trade: Labor Costs as Factor, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Trade: Labor Standards, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Trade: Labor Standards, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Least developed Countries Initiative, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Trade: Licit, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Trade: Job Impact, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Trade: Apparel Figures, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Trade: State Job Loss Charts 1989-1999 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Trade: Mauritius, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Trade: Manufacturing Issues, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Trade: IMF, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Trade: Maryland Fair Trade Campaign, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Trade: Mexico, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Trade: MFA Phase-out, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Trade: Mexico Labor Cases, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Trade: NAFTA 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Trade: NAFTA - AFL-CIO Stuff, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Trade: NAACP, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Trade: NAFTA AFL-CIO Task Force, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Trade: NAFTA - 1997 Latino Study (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Trade: NAFTA Agriculture, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Trade: NAFTA - Agriculture, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Trade: NAFTA Community TAA, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- NAFA: 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Trade: NAFTA: CTC Meeting Notes, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Trade: NAFTA Chapter 11, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Trade: NAFTA Hispanic Letter, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Trade: NAFTA - Administration 3 Year Report & Response, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Trade: NAFTA El Paso, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- NAFTA: EPI Studies, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Trade: NAFTA - EPI Report, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Trade: NAFTA & Florida, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Trade: NAFTA Food Safety, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Trade: NAFTA - Gephardt, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Trade: NAFTA Hinojosa Ojeda Report, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- NAFTA Impact Relief Act: 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Trade: NAFTA Expansion 105th Congress, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Congressional Views, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Trade: NAFTA 105th Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Trade: NAFTA ITC Report, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Trade: NAFTA Job Loss 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Trade: NAFTA Labor Side Agmt., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- NAFTA Lobbying, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Trade: NAFTA - Mexico Labor Law, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Trade - Worker Rights & Trade, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Trade: NAFTA Lobby Reports 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Trade: New Democrats 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Trade: New York Information, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Trade: NAFTA Accountability Act 105th Congress HR978, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- NAFTA Accountability Act, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Trade: NAFTA - Southwest Voter, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Trade: NAFTA - Steelworkers Suit, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Trade: NAFTA TAA, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Trade: NAFTA: Multilateral Agreement on Investigation, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Trade: NAFTA - NAALC, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Trade: NAFTA - Press, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Trade: Public Citizens Materials, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Trade: NAFTA Public Citizen Materials, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Trade: NAFTA Recess Activity, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Trade: NAFTA Testimony, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Trade: NAFTA Trucking, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Trade: NAFTA Trade Deficit, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Trade: NAFTA Vote 1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Trade: NAFTA Opposition Comments, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Trade: NAFTA - Unite Plants Moving, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Trade: Nonenforcement of U.S. Laws, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Trade: North American Agreement on Labor Cooperation, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Trade: Omnibus Bill, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Trade: Omnibus Bill Letters, Etc., 1998 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Trade: Oversupply, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Trade - Olympics, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Trade: Outlook 105th Congress, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Trade: Parliamentarians, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Trade: Personnel, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- PetroChina, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Trade: Phony Numbers, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Trade: Phony Numbers, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Trade: NAFTA - Plant Closings, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Trade: Polling Date 105th Congress, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Trade: Politics, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Trade: Press, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Trade: Prison Labor Ban, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Trade: Public Citizen 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Trade: Public Citizen 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Trade: Public Health, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Trade: Quotas, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Trade: Quota Phase Out, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Trade: Rangel Meeting, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Trade: Remedies, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Trade: Rules of Origin: 1998 Negotiations (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Trade: Safeguard Provisions, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Trade: Sanctions vs. Fig Leaves, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Trade: Section 201, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 47)
- Trade: Segundo Memos, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Trade: Senate Activity 1999 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Trade: Senate Finance 1999 (Box 19, Folder 50)
- Trade: Social Clause, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 51)
- Trade: South Agrees with North, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 52)
- Trade: Spratt Activity, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 53)
- Trade: State Impact, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 54)
- Trade: TAA- Child Support, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 55)
- Trade: TAA 105th Congress, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 56)
- TAA Reauthorizations 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 57)
- TAA, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 58)
- Trade: Textile Trade 105th Congress Votes, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- Trade: Tax Breaks f9or Job Creation, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 60)
- Trade: TAA Figures 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 61)
- Trade: Testimony, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 62)
- Trade: Unite Correspondence, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 63)
- Background: Testimony Report, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 64)
- Trade: Trade Law Major Revisions, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 65)
- Trade: Top 200 Global Corporations, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 66)
- Trade: Unite Positions 105th Congress, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 67)
- Trade: Untie Materials, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 68)
- Trade: Unite Materials CBI & Africa - 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 69)
- Trade: Usbic Primer (Box 19, Folder 70)
- Polls, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Public Citizen, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Trade: Task Force Meetings Notes, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Trade: Votes, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Trade: Worker Rights (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Workers Compensation, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Workers Rights Consortium, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- WTO After China, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Trade: WTO Labor Rights, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Trade: WTO - Levin Resolution, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Trade WTO - Seattle Round, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 11)